

Chukwuemeka Maduekwe

Remotely Available Full Stack Developer











Summary

I'm a proficient Full stack developer with hands-on experience designing, developing and debugging apps using a range of technologies and programming languages. I prefer the Functional paradigm over other paradigms, and I enjoy working on challenging but productive projects. I'm knowledgeable about Web, Mobile and Desktop development. I have confidence in my ability to build apps from scratch with little to no supervision, but, at the same time I enjoy collaboration with other developers.

Preferred Tools

- Frontend: Next.js, React, Svelte and Angular
- **Desktop**: Electron.js
- UI: Material-UI, SASS/SCSS, and CSS3
- Backend: Express (Node.js Framework), Mongo DB, and Firebase
- Mobile: Flutter and React Native

Experience

Frontend Developer at Zenith bank April 2021 till date

- Revamped existing applications, at the same time reducing load time.
- Designed and developed new user-friendly app and improved performance.

Full Stack Developer at SoccerMASS Oct 2018 - June 2021

- Fixed bugs in existing websites and enhanced significant improvement
- Oversaw full lifecycle of webapp development for different projects
- Improved search engine optimization for existing and new sites

System Administrator at Nigeria Security Printing and Minting (intern) 2017

- Installation and configuration of software and hardware
- Manage network servers and setting up of accounts and workstations
- Troubleshoot issues, outages and train staff on new technologies
- Ensure security through access controls, backups and firewalls

Education

Abia state University, Uturu

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (2014 to 2018)